Five years ago, there was a massive fire in Tengu City.
It mainly broke out in a small neighborhood called Nanko.
And that's when I first saw her.
The day she burned my parents alive.
If it's that easy for me to lose control over myself,
I wouldn't be shocked if I already have killed someone.
We'll never know what happened unless Kotari and I both get our memories back.
And until then...
Eventually her power will be too much.
I don't think she'll last longer than two days.
Only one person can save her.
I won't let her die.
His younger sister is a spirit.
He has a friend who is in the AST.
And somehow, Shiro must save them all.
I won't let her die.
Thank you.
Duck, it's swimsuit season, which means you get to see the commander show off her childlike charms as well as her dangerous curves and nothing but two pieces of fabric.
We can't have you getting distracted while you're with Koturi. That would be destructive.
Look, Koturi's fate is on the line here. I'm not going to get the str...
I hope you haven't forgotten that your heart rate is being monitored. You're gawking right now.
Crap, okay, train me!
Can you believe how beautiful these are? Is every one of them called a Mizuki?
Uh, yeah, in Japanese.
But what is it? I mean, what are you supposed to do with it?
Uh, you really don't know? Okay, this is...
Military Zaft Ultimate Grind Instrument. Mizuki for short.
It's a new anti-spirit annihilation suit. When it's activated, the built-in realizer starts the critical driving force, and the warhead is broken into its molecular components and discharged.
It easily cuts through spirit armor, and it destroys the target's body so that it can never be returned to its original state.
What? What's wrong with you?
Oh, look. Hermit.
What are you doing here? What do you want from us? Is it true? Did you bring us here to buy us annihilation suits?
No, she's making that up.
No, I'm not. He knows all about the Mizuki, and he's afraid. He wants to destroy you, that's why you're here.
He was only trying to distract you so it would be easier to make his attack.
I don't believe you! Chita would never do something like that to us!
I don't think he would either.
She's lying. Right, Chita?
No. Origami's telling the truth. I've been trying to figure out an easy way to kill you guys for weeks now.
But why? I don't understand.
I didn't say that. She did.
Why, you little coward! Chita wasn't saying those things! You were just playing a trick on me!
I have no clue what you're talking about.
Kind of a weird coincidence running into you here. Oh, hey, how's your injury?
Oh, I'm all right. However, it's not a coincidence. I'm glad I got to see you, Shido. But Toka's actually the one I'm here to talk to today.
Talk about what?
Some stuff. Do you remember the spirit wearing flames that came down from the sky yesterday?
I know you saw her. I would like you to tell me what you remember.
Hmph! Even if I did know something, you're the last person I would tell!
Pretty please with cherries?
Ah! Stop that! What do you think you're trying to do?
I want you to tell me what you know about the flame spirit. Pretty please?
All right! I'll tell you, but you have to pick your head up. It's confusing!
Yes. I did see the flame spirit.
She was... I don't know.
Very red.
Anything else?
Let me think.
She was also... very strong.
And... is that it?
Um, I was like, whoa, when I saw her.
That doesn't help me.
Oh, really? You're bothering me for an explanation, and now it's not good enough for you?
By the way, Shido, I just realized the only swimsuit I have is the one from the school swim team.
And what that means is it will become quite problematic later if we decide to go to the beach or the pool.
Oh, okay. Well, why don't you just buy one while you're here? Problem solved.
I could, but it's very important to get a second opinion when choosing such things.
Having a male opinion is especially helpful.
I said having a male opinion is helpful.
Oh, well...
Very helpful.
So, are you just trying to get me to check you out?
Now, listen up, origami.
If you want to play that way fine, then whoever excites Shido the most will win a date with him.
Do you really want to waste your time?
I'll never let you go on a date with him. I will win.
What's happening? Why am I suddenly in the middle of a wet t-shirt contest?
Let's go with it. This will be a good training exercise for you.
Oh, my gosh. Is that Shido?
Uh, why is he hanging out in the girls' swimwear section?
That is so lame.
And so it begins.
I hate it. Let's look for something else.
We could try the school swimsuit.
That's so lame.
Wow. Your heart reached through the roof.
Record-breaking numbers. Looks like those girls won the date.
Hey, that is not funny. I'm trying.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Yes? Wonderful choice.
The simple design beautifully highlights Toka's wholesome curves, making her unwittingly arousing.
Good girl.
So what do you think? Tell me. Does it excite you at all?
Uh-huh. What? Yeah.
Yay! I'll try something else then. This was just a warm-up. It gets better.
How's this?
What destructive power she has!
Lovely contrast of dark fabric on Pearl's skin.
An updo with a string halter is always a sassy choice. Fierce!
So what do you think?
Me? Right. I think...
It fits. It looks nice on you.
Well, what's nice got to do with it?
What do you think about this one?
Yes! That's what I'm screaming about!
A knotty body combined with a bashful modesty irresistible!
Over here.
Oh, no! What is she thinking?
Ha! Does this mean you're giving up? I don't blame you.
Ugh.
Huh? Huh?
Take it off.
What?
I'm pretty sure you're not playing by the rules.
And the game just took a surprising turn.
Origami is stimulating him with the art of teasing.
Less is more.
One glimpse and his heart rate has gone through the roof.
Imagination for the win!
So what? I still have more envy! This isn't over yet!
Um, Shido? Will you come here?
I, um, I need your help.
I'm here.
I'm coming in. You're not hurt, are you?
I was trying to get it all by myself, but it's hard to do with just one hand.
Looks like we have a winner. Game over.
Crap.
I don't ever want to go through that again.
I can't say I understand, but at least you had some entertaining commentary, right?
Did it help?
Much better to see those girls there than during a date.
So do you feel like you could handle it now?
For sure.
I'm completely focused on saving Kotari.
Tomorrow it's on.
I won't let her down.
It's just that I wish I could remember.
You know what happened five years ago.
How did I do it?
If I knew how I sealed her powers, maybe this would be easier.
There is one thing we might do to jog your memory.
Would you like to look at the footage of the fire from five years ago?
You have that?
The flames are spreading quickly.
Hot winds are blowing upward.
This has lost aerial footage from one of the networks.
It was never aired.
Ratatisker covered it up pretty well.
Okay, yes.
Here it is.
That's me and Kotari.
Wow.
Now pay close attention.
Pause it!
Wait.
Why?
What did you see?
Is there something I'm missing?
I don't see any movement.
Over there.
Who is that?
Or what is that?
On screen?
What are you talking about?
Behind her!
It's so blurry.
Strange that I can still see a person through all that.
Hey, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Sorry about last night.
Clearly I did more harm than good by showing you that footage.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I want to find out what that image was.
But another time.
I got to focus on this date.
Understood.
We're ready to help anytime you need it.
So have faith in yourself today.
I have to say, I've never seen a more talented playboy.
No spirit stands a chance against your charm.
Thanks.
All right.
Coterie has just been sent to the ground.
She should be arriving very soon.
You got this.
Roger that.
Hey, there you are.
Yep.
Sorry for the wait.
Isn't there something else you'd like to say to me?
Like about the outfit?
I'm pretty sure that's the first thing we taught you.
Yes, you did.
You look great.
Is that for me?
Oh, well, not completely.
I mean, it's not unusual for me to dress up to go out.
But I also had to do something that would let you feel like it's an actual date.
And compliments are nice every once in a while.
All right, come on.
Let's get this date thing started.
Okay.
Yeah, let's!
Oh, boy.
We're gonna have so much fun!
What's going on?
What are you guys doing here?
Oh, guess I forgot to tell you.
The girls will be accompanying you two on your date.
We decided that would be a better plan in the long run.
So, group date, huh?
I love surprises.
How very brave.
I can't wait to see how this turns out.
Shito, look!
I brought the swimsuit you bought yesterday!
The one you loved so much!
Yeah, I brought mine, too.
Hmm.
You all went swimsuit shopping.
How sweet.
Woo-hoo!
Ah!
This is so amazing!
I can't believe they actually have a mountain and a lake inside the building!
There's a lot of water here!
I'm so excited, I can't wait to swim!
Look, another lake!
Can we go swim in that one, please?
Sure, but stay close.
I can't wait!
Let's go, Yoshida!
Okay!
They sure have a lot of energy.
You should have a lot of energy.
Amen!
So what's the deal here?
You're checking out your sister now?
Of course not!
Don't be gross!
You're about to compliment her, right?
She dressed up for you today.
So what's the deal here? You're checking out your sister? Of course not don't be gross. You're about to compliment her, right?
Coterie that's my name so yeah, that swimsuit it looks very nice of your life. I mean you look cute
Right on schedule. Thank you, Shida. Was it Reina or Kanazuki who told you to say that?
Neither I mean it. Yeah, well, then I'm flattered and I'd love to know what you like the most about my look
Everyone your options are there in front of you, so make your picks
Those are all fairly reasonable option one is a given you can't go wrong there
Not number two because that sounds like it's all about the suit and not her and three is just asking for it
You're right about that good point
Option three quick I
I
Really love the way your boobs fill out the top
What did you just say to me nothing? I said you're felt like a mob
What the hell why is everyone freaked out oh so suddenly it's wrong to have a great rack can you hear yourself?
It's like you want to dig for hot springs again. Hey, Shida
You want to try the water slide yeah
I don't want your shenanigans wet again, and I'm way too busy being not five so I'm out
Oh darn guess it's just you and me then this will be so fun
You're right I changed my mind. I want to go
That's much better. Thank you Toka. I wish Coterie would relax and have fun on the date, but this doesn't surprise me
Is there another way to ride? I mean are you sure we're you know safe?
Not really so hold on tight
Hold on tight
That was the best ride ever
Okay, what's wrong?
Look over there
Can you get my ribbons?
It was like woo and then whoa
And then
You are way too wild for me your ribbons are black. I just noticed that there any special reason why do they look that bad?
Of course not. I was just curious
Fine, I'll tell you
Nosey white is a vulnerable color and today I needed to be strong
Black is strong
This is so good. Yes, it is. Thank you. You're welcome. Glad you like it
Hey, Reina what's the reading on Coterie's happiness meter? She looks pissed
It's not going down, but it's not going up either
There's been no change
So that means she hasn't had any fun at all
No way I can seal her powers like this
Are you okay?
Yeah, just went down the wrong pipe I guess
Hold on a sec. Where are you going?
I'm going to use the restroom mother not that it's any of your business
Any other girl would have killed you for asking
What I do I just I thought you and Coterie were getting along again
Are you guys in a fight? It seems like she was mad at you
You look so relieved when she stormed out of here
It's funny how easy to read you are
I'm that obvious?
I need the restroom too
Reina can you tell how freaked out I am?
What are my mental readings right now? Am I that easy to read?
Hey Shido, it's me
I'm sorry, but Reina isn't here to do the analysis
That's weird, where did she go?
No, don't go over there
Does that feel any better?
Yes, much better, thank you
That was a close one, wasn't it?
One more, please
I don't want to risk injecting more
I already gave you 50 times the normal dosage
I don't want to kill you
You really think something like that could kill me?
Drugs don't have a very strong effect in spirit mode
But...
It would help the date with Shido
I mean...
With Big Bro
Please, Reina
I know it's risky, but this might be my last chance to see him
If it fails, I won't be myself anymore after today
But no matter how it turns out, I want to be able to finish my date with him
Be honest with me
How long has Coterie been in that state?
Since the moment she got her spirit powers back
Why didn't you tell me?
Coterie wanted it that way
She asked me not to say anything to you about it
She didn't want you to spend your date feeling sorry for her
If you want to help, pretend that you didn't see any of this
Coterie will appreciate it
Yeah, I will, thank you
Hey
Where'd the girls go?
I don't know, but I think you and I should get dressed and go to the amusement park
Huh?
You got orders from Fraxinus, didn't you?
It's not going well out there, so you might want to take her to ride some rides indoors
Whatever, not like it'll make any difference
You're wrong
Why'd you do that?
I just like the amusement park better than the pool and I'm ready to leave
Really?
We don't have to take Touka and Yoshino
They're having a blast on the Jungle Cruise
Are you ready?
You haven't been here in a while
So prepare to have your mind blown
This is the equipment?
That's right
It's an experimental annihilation suit DW-029, or White Licorice
It has the firepower of an entire AST troop in one monstrous unit
All it would take is one shot
Do you think it would be possible to even defeat Ifrit using this?
Well, if our simulations are accurate, this baby holds enough power to take down a spirit
But that doesn't mean that you're allowed to use it
You don't have the ability or the authorization
A specialist wizard from DEM was crippled after using it on full power for only 30 minutes the first time
Wait, why are you talking about Ifrit?
Oh, I get it
The spirit in the footage was her, right?
It's true there were flames
What footage?
Koturi
I knew it was you
You don't have to touch it
Why would you worship it?
It's so what you said
ganzen it
It's fun
Ifuri
I wish I died
Let's start the key to out.
Thank you.